ELIZABETH JOHNSON

420 Second Lane, Cambridge, MA 93765 e,johnson@myemail.com (753) 155-7551 Empathetic mental health support worker with 2 years of experience counseling vulnerable adults in a residential setting. Excellent awareness of safeguarding best practices with a proven track record for sound decision-making. Strong team player with experience Liaising with outside agencies to create effective and personalized care plans.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SUPPORT WORKER

Jim s Widget Factory, Plano, TX I July 2019 - Present

- Provide emotional and practical support to vulnerable residents experiencing a mental health crisis and refer to external services when appropriate, receiving praise 2x for excellent judgment
- ♦ Administer controlled medications and oversee secure storage, recording doses given with 100% accuracy in 2020
- Coordinate in-house and community activities to enhance client wellbeing and actively research and arrange educational opportunities to promote financial independence
- Encourage and model positive interpersonal relationships and leverage de-escalation techniques to resolve conflicts

SUPPORT WORKER PRECEPT PLACEMENT

Advocates, Cambridge, MA I September 2018 - February 2019

- Supported individuals with brain injuries to help them acquire cnjcial practical and social skills
- ♦ Assisted in planning meetings to generate action plans for each client to meet their needs and promote recovery
- Counseled clients and their family members to develop positive coping strategies and improve mental and physical wellbeing
- Conducted regular safety checks of the residential premises and reported health and safety concerns to the site manager

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ARTS IN PSYCHOLOGY

Cambridge College, Cambridge, MA | September 2015 - June 2019

KEY SKILLS

- Care provision planning
- Mental health support strategies
- Administering medication
- · Record keeping
- · Safeguarding vulnerable adults
- · Written and verbal communication